metblogs.com 2006-06-15

# Metroblogging.com - Think Global. Blog Local.

| 

## 

Terms of Use

Please make sure that you read these Terms of Use carefully before using this site. These Terms of Use apply throughout the site. By using this site, you acknowledge your agreement with these Terms of Use. If you do not agree with any of the below Terms of Use, do not use this site. Metroblogging.com reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update these Terms of Use at any time and your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

TRADEMARKS, COPYRIGHTS AND RESTRICTIONS   
All content is published under a Creative Commons Attribution-NoDerivs-NonCommercial 1.0 license. You are free to copy, distribute, display, and perform the work under the following conditions: Attribution. You must give the original author credit. Noncommercial. You may not use this work for commercial purposes. No Derivative Works. You may not alter, transform, or build upon this work. For any reuse or distribution, you must make clear to others the license terms of this work. Any of these conditions can be waived if you get permission from the author. Your lawyer might enjoy the full legal code which can be found at <http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd-nc/1.0/legalcode>, you probably will not.

LINKED SITES   
Metroblogging.com, whether or not affiliated with sites which may be linked to this site, is not responsible for their content ("Linked Sites"). The Linked Sites are for your convenience only and you access them at your own risk. There is no lifeguard on duty.

DISCLAIMER   
The material that you read on Metroblogging.com is provided solely for entertainment and promotional purposes, however Metroblogging.com does not guarantee any of the content will be entertaining. The information and opinions expressed on the site, in Bulletin Boards, Chat Rooms, or other forums conducted on this site ("Forums") are not necessarily those of Metroblogging.com or its affiliated or related entities or content providers and Metroblogging.com makes no representations or warranties regarding that information or those opinions. Furthermore, neither Metroblogging.com nor its affiliated or related entities or its content providers are responsible or liable to any person or entity whatsoever (including, without limitation, persons who may use or rely on such data/materials or to whom such data/materials may be furnished) for any loss, damage (whether actual, consequential, punitive or otherwise), injury, claim, liability or other cause of any kind or character whatsoever based upon or resulting from any information or opinions provided on Metroblogging.com. If your feel that any of the content on Metroblogging.com is hurtful, Metroblogging.com recommends that you get a hobby and quit taking things so seriously.

SUBMISSIONS   
Although we welcome your comments to this site, Metroblogging.com does not accept unsolicited submissions for the sites or other products. Therefore, you agree not to make any such submissions to Metroblogging.com through this site or otherwise including story ideas, character ideas, plot suggestions, set or costume designs, or scripts. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if, in breach of these Terms of Use, you do send us a submission, you agree not to assert any ownership right of any kind in the submission (including, but not limited to copyright, trademark, unfair competition, moral rights, or implied contract) and you waive the right to receive any financial or other consideration in connection with such unsolicited submission including, but not limited to, credit. If you are very nice we might say "Thanks."

Any notes, message/billboard postings, ideas, suggestions, concepts or other material submitted will become the property of Metroblogging.com throughout the universe and Metroblogging.com shall be entitled to use the material for any type of use forever including in any media whether now known or hereafter devised. While we appreciate your comments, Metroblogging.com cannot make a guarantee that it will respond to your messages. When you submit material to Metroblogging.com, you agree that it has the right to publish the material for any type of use as outlined above including promotional and advertising purposes. 

RULES FOR BULLETIN BOARDS AND CHATROOMS  
Metroblogging.com is not responsible for any material posted on the Bulletin Boards, Chat Rooms, or other forums conducted on this site ("Forums"). You shall not upload, transmit, distribute or otherwise publish through such Forums any content which:  
a) infringes any intellectual property right or any other right of any entity or person, including, but not limited to, violating anyone's copyrights or trademarks;  
b) violates any law; or  
c) advocates illegal activity;   
You agree to indemnify Metroblogging.com for any and all claims, damages, losses, and causes of action arising out of your publication or transmittal of Non-Approved Material or your failure to comply with these Terms of Use. While Metroblogging.com does not and cannot review every message posted by users in the Forums and is not responsible for the content of these messages, Metroblogging.com reserves the right to delete, move, or edit messages that it, in its sole discretion, deems abusive, defamatory, obscene, in violation of copyright or trademark laws, or otherwise unacceptable.

COOPERATION WITH LOCAL, STATE, AND FEDERAL AUTHORITIES  
Unless you're a total knob and Metroblogging.com feels you need to do some hard time in pound me in the ass prison, Metroblogging.com will not cooperate or provide any information to anyone, due in part to the fact that Metroblogging.com does not retain any information about it's users. Due also in part to Metroblogging.com thinking that "the law" going after someone for posting something on the internet is a hunk of crap. Metroblogging.com site administrators are also highly trained ninjas and martial artists who usually like to solve problems on their own.

DENIAL OF ACCESS  
Metroblogging.com, for any reason and at its sole discretion, may decide that any person shall be denied access to any part of the Metroblogging.com Network (a "Denial"). The sending of an e-mail notice by Metroblogging.com to any e-mail address used by the person who is the subject of a Denial shall constitute complete and sufficient notice of the Denial. By agreeing to these Terms of Use, you agree to cease and desist immediately from any attempt to access any part of Metroblogging.com upon issuance to you of a Denial. If you do not so cease and desist, you hereby consent to an injunction, to be entered against you by a court of competent jurisdiction as provided in these Terms of Use, permanently restraining you from attempting to access Metroblogging.com.

SUMMERY  
Play nice, karma is a bitch.

| 

bloggers  
apply  
press  
faq  
advertise  
opml  
contact

| 

## 

Privacy Policy

Metroblogging.com's privacy policy is to respect the privacy of its users.

You are under no obligation to provide personal information in order to use any of our services. For certain areas on Metroblogging.com, we collect personal information only when you provide it to us, for example, if you participate in the comments or message boards. 

The specific user information collected on Metroblogging.com is used only by us. The purpose of collecting such specific information is to enhance the user's experience. Metroblogging.com will never, never, never, never, never, never, never disclose such specific user information unless threatened with jail time or torture based on rapidly decreasing civil liberties, or implementation of "patriotic" laws which are really a sham used by overbearing, power-hungry politicians, in which case there's a very slim chance we might spill everything we can to cover our own ass.

As stated below, Metroblogging.com may share aggregate information about its user's population with third parties. 

The Metroblogging.com Network encourages parents to actively participate with their children on Metroblogging.com, be that by monitoring their usage or flaming them on the comments boards. No persons under the age of 13 or I.Q. of 100 should post any information without their parents or handlers approval and guidance. Additionally, as stated below, we encourage our users to be careful in posting any identifying information in any public forum. 

USE OF IP ADDRESSES   
When ever you are on the Internet, a number (an IP address) is automatically assigned to your computer. This number is identified and logged automatically whenever you visit our Web site. Collecting IP addresses is standard practice on the Internet, and is done automatically by many Web sites. We have been advised that pointing out that everyone else is doing it is supposed to make us feel OK about doing it ourselves. An IP address does not provide us with any of your personally identifiable information, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to us. 

Some software running on Metroblogging.com collects IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, to audit the use of our site, and probably other things we don't even know about. When guests request pages from Metroblogging.com, our servers log the guests' IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our terms of use or to protect our service, site, customers or others. 

USE OF COOKIES   
This is not a kitchen so, regretfully, we are not talking about the tasty desert treats. Cookies are pieces of information that a Website transfers to an individual's computer for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are an industry standard used by most Web sites, including ours, can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. Electronic Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files whereas baked ones, depending on their usage, might. 

We use cookies in our discussion areas to eliminate the need to log in every time you use the comments and other message boards on our Web site. You must opt in by selecting "Remember me" in order to use cookies. No cookies will be used without your request. You can set your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you aren't doing this, you should, you'd be surprised as how much crap that web sites try to store on your computer.

You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Metroblogging.com does not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. 

AGGREGATED INFORMATION   
We collect information through our Web site relating to traffic levels on our Web site - for example, the total number of users visiting particular pages. We also aggregate demographic information and the results of surveys. 

This aggregated information, which does not personally identify you, is helpful to us for improving the services we offer and for marketing purposes. We may share aggregated information with our advertisers, business partners, or other companies, and may post it online with the intention of rubbing our kick ass numbers in the faces of lesser trafficked Web Sites.

PUBLIC FORUMS/CHATS   
We make discussion areas and chat forums available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. No matter how enticing the offer sounds, posting your banking info to a message board is never, NEVER a good idea.

LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES   
Users should be aware that when you are on Metroblogging.com, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. Metroblogging.com has no responsibility for these cookies. There are millions of Web Sites on the internet and if you think we are responsible for what goes on on any other Web Site you must be smoking crack.

Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online --- for example, via message boards or chat --- that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. We cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. Don't be an idiot and you shouldn't have any problems.

Metroblogging.com's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet and therefore beyond our control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS   
By using this site, you signify your assent to Bloggin.la's Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of Metroblogging.com following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. If terms are modified a third time, and your usage continues, so will your acceptance of the thirdly modified terms.

|   
---|---|---|---|---
